<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[The stories of food, life, universe and science, i.e., everything]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The stories of food, life, universe and science, i.e., everything]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/composite-eater/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 12:19:39 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/composite-eater/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Butchers.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Butchers.</h1><p>I don't like killing. There is no pride in ending the life of anything or anybody. It's no fun either, although staying out in the cold for hours waiting for that wild boar to go on a midnight stroll by the moon instills that special feeling. A poet would call it a connection with the original human. He would call upon the blood and the god-like decisions about the life and death. I'm sorry, I'm not a poet.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/29a62f51-c74e-4b47-b72e-24921ce8abba.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/29a62f51-c74e-4b47-b72e-24921ce8abba.jpg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">953f62c3-7a3f-4c14-a804-0969e9bcc604</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 20:17:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Culinary hide and seek]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Culinary hide and seek</h1><p>After a warm winter full of carrots, potatoes, apples, pears and more apples, the spring has finally come to Compiègne, Picardie, France. But it took it's time, no worries, apparently. As in 2012, the so-called "spring months" had temperatures comparable with those on the other side of the Atlantic Ocean. Suddenly, I wasn't sure if I'm in France or back in Montréal. But at last, the sun, though still somewhat shy, has encouraged me past Saturday to replenish the provisions, maintained at a bare survival level, due to some voyages (in search of the sun, besides of other goals). Please feel free to amuse yourself in finding some of the more and less fresh arrivals from the Picardian terroir. May I say, that the colinot (European hake, Merluccius merluccius), was especially fresh, simply put in the oven for a slight roast and devoured with oven-hot baguette drowning in extra vergine. What will the next Saturday bring?</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/844dca48-a20b-452d-9c80-ad6420e8c9f9.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/composite-eater/culinary-hide-and-seek/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">26cd8a12-b49b-4e88-af5d-f4e27383e438</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 15:10:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>